Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Personalities, circa 1930s - 1970s; 2 (Box 1554)
    - Mrs. Peale, head of R. Digest [The Reader's Digest], and LT, 1
    - Verso: Mrs. Peale, head of R. Digest [The Reader's Digest], and LT, 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas talking with three others], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man and woman], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas having lunch with two people], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas eating with a man and a woman], 5
    - Announcement of gifts of $1,000,000 toward the three-year goal of $15,000,000 to rehabilitate and expand the eight members of the Near East College Association was made by Lowell Thomas, fund chairman, tonight at a dinner honoring Dr. Allen O. Whipple, eminent American Surgeon. Dr. Whipple leaves for Lebanon shortly as advisor to the new Dodge Medical Center of the American University of Beirut, one of the largest single objectives of the fund. Dr. Whipple, retiring this year from Columbia University and Presbyterian Hospital, received tributes for his career in medicine from many persons of prominence at the dinner attended by Hon. Joseph C. Grew, Former Undersecretary of State; Madame Bechara El-Khouri, wife of the President of Lebanon; Allen W. Dulles, President of the Near East College Association; George Wadsworth, U.S. Minister to Syria and Lebanon; Photo Gratis for immediate release courtesy fund for Near East College Assn.; Photo shows: Left to right, Dr. Allen O. Whipple, Joseph C. Grew, Allen W. Dulles and Lowell Thomas., 6
    - Note: Announcement of gifts of $1,000,000 toward the three-year goal of $15,000,000 to rehabilitate and expand the eight members of the Near East College Association was made by Lowell Thomas, fund chairman, tonight at a dinner honoring Dr. Allen O. Whipple, eminent American Surgeon. Dr. Whipple leaves for Lebanon shortly as advisor to the new Dodge Medical Center of the American University of Beirut, one of the largest single objectives of the fund. Dr. Whipple, retiring this year from Columbia University and Presbyterian Hospital, received tributes for his career in medicine from many persons of prominence at the dinner attended by Hon. Joseph C. Grew, Former Undersecretary of State; Madame Bechara El-Khouri, wife of the President of Lebanon; Allen W. Dulles, President of the Near East College Association; George Wadsworth, U.S. Minister to Syria and Lebanon; Photo Gratis for immediate release courtesy fund for Near East College Assn.; Photo shows: Left to right, Dr. Allen O. Whipple, Joseph C. Grew, Allen W. Dulles and Lowell Thomas., 7
    - Bernt Balchen, LT, Erling Strom, 8
    - Verso: Bernt Balchen, LT, Erling Strom, 8-verso
    - Ali Khan and LT, others do not know, 9
    - Verso: Ali Khan and LT, others do not know, 9-verso
    - Robert Trout, ?, ?, LT, ?, ?, 10
    - Verso: Robert Trout, ?, ?, LT, ?, ?, 10-verso
    - LT - where?, 11
    - Verso: LT - where?, 11-verso
    - John Royal (of NBC) - left, Hamilton Fish - right, 12
    - Verso: John Royal (of NBC) - left, Hamilton Fish - right, 12-verso
    - L to R Toni [Mott], L.T., Sepp Ruschp, ?, skiing, 13
    - Verso: L to R Toni [Mott], L.T., Sepp Ruschp, ?, skiing, 13-verso
    - Archbishop Athenagoris and LT, 14
    - Verso: Archbishop Athenagoris and LT, 14-verso
    - Archbishop Athenagoris and LT, 15
    - Left to Right: Arkedis, Feeley, Thomas, Knudsen, 16
    - Verso: Left to Right: Arkedis, Feeley, Thomas, Knudsen, 16-verso
    - Roscoe Drummond, columnist, L.T. and Geo. Mardikian, 17
    - Verso: Roscoe Drummond, columnist, L.T. and Geo. Mardikian, 17-verso
  - Subject files: Personalities, circa 1930s - 1978; 3 (Box 1554)
    - Astronaut Col. Frank Borman, Waldorf- Dr. Peale, banquet - Apr. 1970, 1
    - Verso: Astronaut Col. Frank Borman, Waldorf- Dr. Peale, banquet - Apr. 1970, 1-verso
    - Sen. Saltonstall - right, 2
    - Verso: Sen. Saltonstall - right, 2-verso
    - [?] Dean Yeagge, 1974, 3
    - Verso: [?] Dean Yeagge, 1974, 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving an award], 4
    - Harriman, Drew Pearson, LT, Black?, 5
    - Verso: Harriman, Drew Pearson, LT, Black?, 5-verso
    - With Admiral Byrd at Ford Exhibit, World's Fair in Flushing Meadow, 6
    - Verso: With Admiral Byrd at Ford Exhibit, World's Fair in Flushing Meadow, 6-verso
    - Jack Schneider, 7
    - Verso: Jack Schneider, 7-verso
    - [Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas], 8
    - Lowell Thomas, 9
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas, 9-verso
    - Miss Ohta, Mrs. Yakowa, 10
    - Verso: Miss Ohta, Mrs. Yakowa, 10-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Miss Ohta and Mrs. Yakowa], 11
    - Verso: Miss Ohta, Mrs. Yakowa, 11-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with Miss Ohta and Mrs. Yakowa], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas and two other men at an event], 13
    - [Herbert Hoover, center, Lowell Thomas, right], 14
    - Elmer Bobst ( Horatio Alger, 1974), 15
    - Verso: Elmer Bobst ( Horatio Alger, 1974), 15-verso
    - [Harry G. Thomas and Lowell Thomas, front, Herbert Hoover, second from right, rear], 16
    - (on left Michel Halbouty) L.T. shaking hands with Robt. G. Dunlap, Pres. Of Sun Oil Co., 17
    - Verso: (on left Michel Halbouty) L.T. shaking hands with Robt. G. Dunlap, Pres. Of Sun Oil Co., 17-verso
    - Arthur "Bugs" Baer; some chap who was featured by Ripley in his Believe-It-Or-Not cartoon, a man who hadn't done anything, hadn't played baseball, hadn't been married, hadn't been to a World's Fair etc,; Olsen of Hellzapoppin' and L.T., 18
    - Note: Arthur "Bugs" Baer; some chap who was featured by Ripley in his Believe-It-Or-Not cartoon, a man who hadn't done anything, hadn't played baseball, hadn't been married, hadn't been to a World's Fair etc,; Olsen of Hellzapoppin' and L.T., 19
    - Col. L.CD. Mallory, Bob McRavey [?], and LT, 20
    - Verso: Col. L.CD. Mallory, Bob McRavey [?], and LT, 20-verso
    - ITALY - Leone Valmaggia (Team Captain), Romolo De Sisti, Lowell Thomas, Franco Bertola and Talisio Tirinnanzi., 21
    - Verso: ITALY - Leone Valmaggia (Team Captain), Romolo De Sisti, Lowell Thomas, Franco Bertola and Talisio Tirinnanzi., 21-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with three others at an event], 22
    - [Lowell Thomas dressed up on stage], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas, left, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, right], 24
    - [Mrs. Marianna Thomas, center, Lowell Thomas, right], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and two friends], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a crown while he gives a speech], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a banquet table], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man at an event], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with others on stage], 30
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking a man's hand], 31
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men and a woman], 32
    - Please Ask head of winds Club! [Lowell Thomas and two pilots standing in front of a plane], 33
    - Verso: Please Ask head of winds Club!, 33-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas holding a medal with two other people], 34
    - [Lowell Thoma standing with three other men], 35
    - [Lowell Thomas speaking with a man], 36
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photographs], circa 1930s - 1978; 4 (Box 1554)
    - [?] Gov. of Ohio and LT, 1
    - Verso: [?] Gov. of Ohio and LT, 1-verso
    - SALUTE TO SARNOFF More than 1,000 leaders of science, industry, government and religion gathered in New York tonight (Sept. 30) for an unprecedented salute to Gen. David Sarnoff, father of American television and chairman of the Radio Corporation of America. Gen. Sarnoff, who started his communications career on Sept. 30, 1906 as an office boy for the Marconi Wireless Telegraph Company of America, was honored with a 60th anniversary dinner at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel. Three national organizations - Electronic Industries Association (EIA), the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE), and the National Association of Broadcasters (NAB) - joined forces to co-sponsor the "Salute to David Sarnoff." Gen. Sarnoff receives a gold medallion from toastmaster Lowell Thomas, while Vincent Wasilewski, president of NAB, holds a scroll citing Sarnoff accomplishments. At right is Frederick R. Kappel, chairman, American Telephone and Telegraph Company. At rear, from left, are Dr. Jerome Wiesner, provost and dean of Massachusetts Institute of Technology, representing IEEE; William S. Paley, chairman, Columbia Broadcasting System, representing NAB; and Walter K. MacAdam, vice president of IEEE. Altho' LT had left N.B.C. and gone over to CBS 20 years before this event Gen. Sarnoff asked him to be the toastmaster., 2
    - Note: SALUTE TO SARNOFF More than 1,000 leaders of science, industry, government and religion gathered in New York tonight (Sept. 30) for an unprecedented salute to Gen. David Sarnoff, father of American television and chairman of the Radio Corporation of America. Gen. Sarnoff, who started his communications career on Sept. 30, 1906 as an office boy for the Marconi Wireless Telegraph Company of America, was honored with a 60th anniversary dinner at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel. Three national organizations - Electronic Industries Association (EIA), the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE), and the National Association of Broadcasters (NAB) - joined forces to co-sponsor the "Salute to David Sarnoff." Gen. Sarnoff receives a gold medallion from toastmaster Lowell Thomas, while Vincent Wasilewski, president of NAB, holds a scroll citing Sarnoff accomplishments. At right is Frederick R. Kappel, chairman, American Telephone and Telegraph Company. At rear, from left, are Dr. Jerome Wiesner, provost and dean of Massachusetts Institute of Technology, representing IEEE; William S. Paley, chairman, Columbia Broadcasting System, representing NAB; and Walter K. MacAdam, vice president of IEEE. Altho' LT had left N.B.C. and gone over to CBS 20 years before this event Gen. Sarnoff asked him to be the toastmaster., 3
    - Caption: New York, March 29 - TETE A TETE - Commentator Lowell Thomas leans over for a word with Washington society hostess Perle Mesta during a reception at the Thomas A. Dooley Foundation dinner dance at New York's Plaza Hotel Wednesday night. They were both presented "Splendid Americans" awards by the foundation. 1972, 4
    - [Duke Kahanamoku and Lowell Thomas], [2 copies], 5
    - Armand Hammer and LT, 6
    - Verso: Armand Hammer and LT, 6-verso
    - Caption: (MH1) MIAMI, April 14 -- GETTING TO THE SEAT OF THE PROBLEM -- Mohan, a 1,500 pound baby rhinocerous from Nepal, starred in a Lowell Thomas film and then was donated to the Crandon Park Zoo in Miami. Thomas, a world-famed newscaster, showed up with a bunch of greenery for Mohan during a visit to Miami. But Mohan showed his gratitude by biting Thomas on the seat of the pants. 1971, 7
    - [2 copies] Herb Shriner and LT giving award to the air line hostess of the year. Her name: -, 8
    - Verso: Herb Shriner and LT giving award to the air line hostess of the year. Her name: -, 8-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with others behind mics], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a man and woman shaking hands], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas and a woman with a shash that says "Western"], 11
    - [left to right: Lowell Thomas, Lewis Young, Helen Thomas, unidentified man, Charles Kuralt], 12
    - Clement Stone, 13
    - Verso: Clement Stone, 13-verso
    - LT, Geo. "Dick" Richards, Gov. Kim Ziegler, 14
    - Verso: LT, Geo. "Dick" Richards, Gov. Kim Ziegler, 14-verso
    - "Pete" Conrad, 15
    - Verso: "Pete" Conrad, 15-verso
    - Lanny Ross, LT and Ben Grauer, 16
    - Verso: Lanny Ross, LT and Ben Grauer, 16-verso
    - Tom Harmon, Jack Simplot and LT, 17
    - Verso: Tom Harmon, Jack Simplot and LT, 17-verso
    - Tom Harmon, Jack Simplot, Geo. Weller, Jane Salisbury and L.T., 18
    - Verso: Tom Harmon, Jack Simplot, Geo. Weller, Jane Salisbury and L.T., 18-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a woman], 19
    - [2 copies], [Lowell Thomas at a sporting event (?)], 20
    - Edgar Bergen, Harry Von Zell, 21
    - Verso: Edgar Bergen, Harry Von Zell, 21-verso
    - Floyd Odlum, L.T., Jackie Cochran, 22
    - Verso: Floyd Odlum, L.T., Jackie Cochran, 22-verso
    - Left [?] Aylesworth, Pres. Of N.B.C. Last three figures: Dr. Francis P. Gaines, LT, Mrs. DuPont, 23
    - Verso: Left [?] Aylesworth, Pres. Of N.B.C. Last three figures: Dr. Francis P. Gaines, LT, Mrs. DuPont, 23-verso
    - After all he's only in his 90th year! [Lowell Thomas with unidentified woman], 24
    - Verso: After all he's only in his 90th year! [Lowell Thomas with unidentified woman], 24-verso
    - [Two women talking next to a man], 25
    - [Lowell Tholmas sitting next to a man giving a speech], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas and two men], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a woman], 28
    - [People sitting at a table at an event], 29
    - [Party guests chatting], 30
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photograph], circa 1930s - 1970s; 5 (Box 1554)
    - John Murchison and LT, 1
    - Verso: John Murchison and LT, 1-verso
    - Dick Hauserman; LT; and John Murchison., 2
    - Verso: Dick Hauserman; LT; and John Murchison., 2-verso
    - Gen. Robt Lee Bullard and LT, 3
    - Verso: Gen. Robt Lee Bullard and LT, 3-verso
    - Lord Thomson of Fleet and L.T., 4
    - Verso: Lord Thomson of Fleet and L.T., 4-verso
    - Lord Thomson of Fleet and L.T., 5
    - Verso: Lord Thomson of Fleet and L.T., 5-verso
    - LT and Admiral Reedy, 6
    - Verso: LT and Admiral Reedy, 6-verso
    - Pres. David O. McKay and LT - Salt Lake City [2 copies], 7
    - Verso: Pres. David O. McKay and LT - Salt Lake City, 7-verso
    - With Lady Wilkins, wife of his old friend, Sir Hubert Wilkins [2 copies], 8
    - Verso: With Lady Wilkins, wife of his old friend, Sir Hubert Wilkins, 8-verso
    - Caption: To Lowell Thomas, with every good wish, [signed] James A. Farley; Verso: Sen. Robt Taft, Jim Farley, L.T., Tom - "Collier", 9
    - Verso: Sen. Robt Taft, Jim Farley, L.T., Tom - "Collier", 9-verso
    - Univ. of Calif Radiation Lab, Ed McMillan - Nobel Prize [?], 10
    - Verso: Univ. of Calif Radiation Lab, Ed McMillan - Nobel Prize [?], 10-verso
    - LT and Mac Miller in Alaska, 11
    - Verso: LT and Mac Miller in Alaska, 11-verso
    - LT in Europe - Genoa (?) with ?, 12
    - Verso: LT in Europe - Genoa (?) with ?, 12-verso
    - LT and a GM Exec? [Henry Kissinger?], 13
    - Verso: LT and a GM Exec? [Henry Kissinger?], 13-verso
    - Earl Thacker and LT - Hawaii, 14
    - Verso: Earl Thacker and LT - Hawaii, 14-verso
    - Earl Thacker and LT - Hawaii, 15
    - Mr. Goldwyn and L.T., 16
    - Verso: Mr. Goldwyn and L.T., 16-verso
    - [Verso: March - 1958], 17
    - Verso: March - 1958, 17-verso
    - Lowell Thomas and another men behind a CBS microphone], 18
    - [Banquet], 19
    - [Banquet], 20
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a banquet table], 21
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photograph], circa 1930s - 1980; 6 (Box 1554)
    - Last three figures: Dr. Francis P. Gaines, LT, Mrs. DuPont, on left Deals Aylesworth, first pres. of N.B.C., 1
    - Verso: Last three figures: Dr. Francis P. Gaines, LT, Mrs. DuPont, on left Deals Aylesworth, first pres. of N.B.C., 1-verso
    - Gov. Edison of N.J. on right, 2
    - Verso: Gov. Edison of N.J. on right, 2-verso
    - Dr. Ochsner, 3
    - Verso: Dr. Ochsner, 3-verso
    - Sheila Scott [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 4
    - Verso: Sheila Scott [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 4-verso
    - Sheila Scott [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 5
    - Verso: Sheila Scott [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 5-verso
    - Sheila Scott [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 6
    - Verso: Sheila Scott [James H. "Jimmy" Doolittle, left, Lowell Thomas, right], 6-verso
    - Farley guest speaker at New York Ad club New York, N.Y. James A. Farley (seated right) is shown at a meeting of the New York Advertising Club, Nov. 7, at which he was a guest speaker. Lawrence Robert (seated left), treasurer, Democratic National Committee; Lew Lehr (standing left), radio and screen comedian; and Lowell Thomas (standing right), radio commentator, are shown with Farley. 11-7-38, 7
    - Note: Farley guest speaker at New York Ad club New York, N.Y. James A. Farley (seated right) is shown at a meeting of the New York Advertising Club, Nov. 7, at which he was a guest speaker. Lawrence Robert (seated left), treasurer, Democratic National Committee; Lew Lehr (standing left), radio and screen comedian; and Lowell Thomas (standing right), radio commentator, are shown with Farley. 11-7-38, 8
    - L. to R. Front row: Fred Hinton, Lowell Thomas Sr., Noel Wien, Back Row: Joe Jacquot, Cecil Rhode, W.C. "Bill" Bishop, Bob Reeve, 9
    - Verso: L. to R. Front row: Fred Hinton, Lowell Thomas Sr., Noel Wien, Back Row: Joe Jacquot, Cecil Rhode, W.C. "Bill" Bishop, Bob Reeve, 9-verso
    - Marshall Guthrie, Admiral Moran, LT, 10
    - Verso: Marshall Guthrie, Admiral Moran, LT, 10-verso
    - Gretchen Fraser - Am. 1st Winter Olympic Gold Medal winner. Otto Lang - Sun Valley, Ida. Director and Producer of Cinerama; Gretchen Fraser, first American ever to win a gold medal in a winter Olympics. With LT and famous veteran skier, Otto Lang., 11
    - Verso: Gretchen Fraser - Am. 1st Winter Olympic Gold Medal winner. Otto Lang - Sun Valley, Ida. Director and Producer of Cinerama; Gretchen Fraser, first American ever to win a gold medal in a winter Olympics. With LT and famous veteran skier, Otto Lang., 11-verso
    - Left to Right: General R.A. Knobloch, Lowell Thomas, Joe Doolittle, General James Doolittle, 12
    - Verso: Left to Right: General R.A. Knobloch, Lowell Thomas, Joe Doolittle, General James Doolittle, 12-verso
    - Jim Thorpe in background Mayor Jimmy Walker - Gen. Claire Chenault, 13
    - Verso: Jim Thorpe in background Mayor Jimmy Walker - Gen. Claire Chenault, 13-verso
    - with Norman Rockwell, 14
    - Verso: with Norman Rockwell, 14-verso
    - L.T., Norman Rockwell, 15
    - Verso: L.T., Norman Rockwell, 15-verso
    - Dr. P.S. Gill, L.T., Norman Rockwell [4 copies], 16
    - Verso: Dr. P.S. Gill, L.T., Norman Rockwell, 16-verso
    - Dr. P.S. Gill, L.T., Norman Rockwell, 17
    - Verso: Dr. P.S. Gill, L.T., Norman Rockwell, 17-verso
    - [Dr. P.S. Gill, L.T., Norman Rockwell], 18
    - Roosevelt, Thomas [Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. and Mrs. Roosevelt], 19
    - Verso: Roosevelt, Thomas [Lowell Thomas, Mrs. Frances Ryan Thomas, Theodore Roosevelt, Jr. and Mrs. Roosevelt], 19-verso
    - Left to Right:- Mrs. Thomas, LT, Mrs. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., General Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., 20
    - Verso: Left to Right:- Mrs. Thomas, LT, Mrs. Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., General Theodore Roosevelt, Jr., 20-verso
    - Barry Ferris, left, head of INS, Joe Connolly - head of Hearst empire, 21
    - Verso: Barry Ferris, left, head of INS, Joe Connolly - head of Hearst empire, 21-verso
    - Caption: To Lowell Thomas with the admiration, thanks and deep affection of one who has the honor to call him friend, [signed] John Creighton Murray. 2-12-80, 22
    - [Lowell Thoms standing with two men], 23
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man], 24
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with two men], 25
    - [Lowell Thomas and three others each holding a snake], 26
    - [Lowell Thomas reading a speech from behind an NBC microphone], 27
    - [Lowell Thomas an a man looking at a document], 28
    - [Lowell Thomas talking to a man], 29
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with a group of men. Air service post event (?)], 30
  Box 1555
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Personalities [includes color photographs], circa 1923 - 1970s; 1 (Box 1555)
    - Dr. Ralph C. Hutchison, LT, LT Jr., Thomas J. Watson, Sr. The 2 seniors were receiving honorary degrees at "W + J" Univ. He now has some 30 Ph.D. degrees, 1
    - Verso: Dr. Ralph C. Hutchison, LT, LT Jr., Thomas J. Watson, Sr. The 2 seniors were receiving honorary degrees at "W + J" Univ. He now has some 30 Ph.D. degrees, 1-verso
    - Father Hesburgh, Actress Irene Dunne, Mr. and Mrs. Jack (CBS), 2
    - Verso: Father Hesburgh, Actress Irene Dunne, Mr. and Mrs. Jack (CBS), 2-verso
    - LOWELL THOMAS RECEIVES AMERICAN LEGION PUBLIC RELATIONS AWARD - Veteran reporter and commentator Lowell Thomas is presented the 1972 American Legion National Commander's Public Relations Award by National Commander John H. Geiger, of Des Plaines, Ill., at the Legion's annual Public Relations Luncheon held March 1, 1972. Newsman Thomas was cited for "his pioneering efforts in the audio visual field as a commentator and lecturer on our world" and for bringing to the people of the world "a greater understanding of diverse lands and cultures." The Legion's Public Relations Luncheon was held in conjunction with the organization's 12th annual Washington Conference, February 27 - March 3. Shown Left to Right are: National Commander John H. Geiger; Auxiliary National President Bertha Parker; Lowell Thomas; U.S. Secret Service Director, James J. Rowley; Legion National Adjutant, William F. Hauck, 3
    - Verso: LOWELL THOMAS RECEIVES AMERICAN LEGION PUBLIC RELATIONS AWARD - Veteran reporter and commentator Lowell Thomas is presented the 1972 American Legion National Commander's Public Relations Award by National Commander John H. Geiger, of Des Plaines, Ill., at the Legion's annual Public Relations Luncheon held March 1, 1972. Newsman Thomas was cited for "his pioneering efforts in the audio visual field as a commentator and lecturer on our world" and for bringing to the people of the world "a greater understanding of diverse lands and cultures." The Legion's Public Relations Luncheon was held in conjunction with the organization's 12th annual Washington Conference, February 27 - March 3. Shown Left to Right are: National Commander John H. Geiger; Auxiliary National President Bertha Parker; Lowell Thomas; U.S. Secret Service Director, James J. Rowley; Legion National Adjutant, William F. Hauck, 3-verso
    - Walter Winchell - left, 4
    - Verso: Walter Winchell - left, 4-verso
    - Walter Hagen, 5
    - Verso: Walter Hagen, 5-verso
    - Verso: Dr. Francis P. Gaines, Pres. Of Wash and Lee, Mrs. DuPont, 6
    - Verso: Dr. Francis P. Gaines, Pres. Of Wash and Lee, Mrs. DuPont, 6-verso
    - Sidney Smith - "The Gumps"; Sidney Smith and Jack Harding, 7
    - Verso: Sidney Smith - "The Gumps"; Sidney Smith and Jack Harding, 7-verso
    - Sidney Smith + Jack Harding, 8
    - Verso: Sidney Smith + Jack Harding, 8-verso
    - Withers, Skinner, Thomas, Dawson, 9
    - Verso: Withers, Skinner, Thomas, Dawson, 9-verso
    - Elsa Maxwell - left., 10
    - Verso: Elsa Maxwell - left., 10-verso
    - LT with King of Greece and Elsa Maxwell; LT has spoken to thousands of live audiences all over the world - and has been toastmaster at 100's of banquets., 11
    - Verso: LT with King of Greece and Elsa Maxwell; LT has spoken to thousands of live audiences all over the world - and has been toastmaster at 100's of banquets., 11-verso
    - LT and Semon E. Knudsen, Executive Vice President of General Motors [looks like young Henry Kissinger], 12
    - Verso: LT and Semon E. Knudsen, Executive Vice President of General Motors [looks like young Henry Kissinger], 12-verso
    - Caption: To Lowell and Mrs. Thomas, Affectionately, Father Ted Hesburgh; Verso: Pres. Notre Dame [Theodore Hesburgh], 13
    - Verso: Pres. Notre Dame [Theodore Hesburgh], 13-verso